let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is smallest country in the world?",
    answer: "Vatican",
    options: [
      "Belize",
      "Andorra",
      "Vatican",
      "Cyprus"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the most populated city in Africa?",
    answer: "Lagos",
    options: [
      "Lagos",
      "Cairo",
      "Casablanca",
      "Johannesburg"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the country that have its map on its flag?",
    answer: "Cyprus",
    options: [
      "Bermuda",
      "Tonga",
      "Tasmania",
      "Cyprus"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which one of these lakes is largest in Africa",
    answer: "Lake Victoria",
    options: [
      "Lake Tchad ",
      "Lake Victoria",
      "Lake Malawi",
      "Lake Assal"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "We love to visit them, but what’s the correct definition of an archipelago?",
    answer: "A cluster or group of many islands",
    options: [
      "A section of land almost fully surrounded by water",
      "A small, low elevation island on a coral reef",
      "A large headland extending into a body of water",
      "A cluster or group of many islands"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " how many countries sit along the equator?",
    answer: "13",
    options: [
      "9",
      "13",
      "15",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " Which country’s territory is geographically closest to the North Pole?",
    answer: "Canada",
    options: [
      "Canada",
      "iceland",
      "Norway",
      "Russia"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Fossils can be found all over the world, but can you guess the age of the oldest fossil ever found?",
    answer: "Over 3.5 billion years old",
    options: [
      "1 billion years old",
      "300 million years old",
      "900 million years old",
      "Over 3.5 billion years old"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: " In Iceland, you can walk across two tectonic plates, side by side. Which ones, exactly?",
    answer: "Eurasian and North American",
    options: [
      "Eurasian and Antarctic",
      "Eurasian and North American",
      "Eurasian and South American",
      "Eurasian and Indo-Australian"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "UNESCO protects the world’s most important sites. How many World Heritage Sites have they inscribed?",
    answer: "1121",
    options: [
      "2345",
      "1121",
      "1888",
      "951"
    ]
  },
  
];